Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Organizations PE.036
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- N, 1899-2012; 18.5 Linear Feet in 16 record cartons, 3 manuscript boxes, 2 oversize shared boxes, and 1 shared manuscript box
  - Non-Collaboration (New York, NY), circa 1971 (Box 75)
  - Non-Intervention in Chile, 1978 (Box 75)
  - Non-Partisan Committee for Ratification of the Federal Child Labor Amendment, 1935- (Box 75)
  - Non-Partisan Council to Win the Peace, 1944 (Box 75)
  - Non-Partisan Labor Defense, 1936, undated (Box 75)
  - Non-Partisan Students League (University of Chicago, IL), 1950 (Box 75)
  - Non-Sectarian Anti-Nazi League to Champion Human Rights, 1938 (Box 75)
  - Nontraditional Employment for Women (New York, NY), 2000- (Box 75)
  - noRNC Housing Working Group, undated (Box 127, Folder 49)
  - North American Anarchist Gathering (Lawrence, KS), 2002 (Box 75)
  - North American Anarchist Network, undated (Box 75)
  - North American Congress on Latin America I, 1968-1970 (Box 75, Box 127, Folder 50)
  - North American Congress on Latin America II, 1970- (Box 75)
  - North American Greek Relief Fund (New York, NY), 1974 (Box 75)
  - North American League for Immigrants (Boston, MA), undated (Box 75)
  - North American Student Cooperative League (Chicago, IL), 1957 (Box 75)
  - North American Student Cooperative Organization I, 1971-1980 (Box 75)
  - North American Student Cooperative Organization II, 1971-1980 (Box 75)
  - North American Unemployed and Welfare Rights Organization, 1973-1974, undated (Box 75)
  - North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO), undated (Box 127, Folder 51)
  - North Suburban Coalition Against the War in Vietnam, 1969 (Box 75)
  - Northeast Labor Committee for Global Justice (Boston, MA), 2001 (Box 75)
  - Northeastern Anarchist Network, 2007, undated (Box 75)
  - Northeastern Federation of Anarchist-Communists, 2003-2008 (Box 75)
  - Northern Book House, 1963, undated (Box 75)
  - Northern California Alliance (San Francisco, CA), 1976 (Box 75)
  - Northern Dispensary (New York, NY), 1828, 1939 (Box 75)
  - Northern Ireland Civil Rights Association, 1972 (Box 75)
  - Northern Neighbors/ Northern Book House (Ontario, Canada) I, 1965- (Box 75)
  - Northern Neighbors/ Northern Book House (Ontario, Canada) II, 1965- (Box 75)
  - Northern States Women's Co-operative Guild (Superior, WI), undated (Box 75)
  - Northern Student Movement (New York, NY), 1962-1963 (Box 75)
  - Northland Poster Collective (Minneapolis, MN), 1999- (Box 75)
  - Northwest Extra, 2001- (Box 75)
  - Not for Profit TV (New York, NY), undated (Box 75)
  - Not in Our Name (New York, NY), 1984 (Box 75)
    Materials in this file are related to the women's liberation movement.
  - Not in Our Name, 2001-, undated (Box 75)
  - Not with Our Money!, 2002, undated (Box 75)
    Materials in this file are related to prison funding.
  - Notting Hill Women's Liberation (Box 75)
  - Nov 4 Committee, 1973, undated (Box 75)
  - November 4th Coalition, circa 1970s (Box 75)
    Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection of Oversized Material (PE 040) also contains a November 4th Coalition file.
  - November 8 Mobilization Committee, 1966 (Box 75)
  - November Action Coalition (Massachusetts Institute of Technology), 1969, undated (Box 75)
  - NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund (New York, NY), 1986- (Box 75)
  - Nuclear Age Peace Fund, 1989 (Box 75)
  - Nuclear Weapons Freeze Campaign (St. Louis, MO), 1987- (Box 75)
  - NYC Free Events Calendar, 2000- (Box 75)
  - NYC Grassroots Media, 2004 (Box 75, Box 128, Folder 1)
  - NYC People's Referendum on Free Trade, 2008- (Box 75)
  - NYC Student and Youth Solidarity Network, undated (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - NYU Women's Liberation, undated (Box 75)
- O, 1901-2013; 4.5 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 1 manuscript box
  - Oberlin Wages for Housework Collective, undated (Box 76)
  - Observateur des Deux Mondes (Paris, France), 1948 (Box 76)
  - Occupy Wall Street, 2013 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - October 4th Organization, 1970s (Box 76)
  - October 10th Coalition, 2008 (Box 76)
  - October 14th Coalition, 1972 (Box 76)
  - October 22nd Coalition to Stop Police Brutality, Repression, and the Criminalization of a Generation, 1997, undated (Box 76)
  - October Coalition, undated (Box 76)
  - October League (Marxist-Leninist) I, 1972-1976 (Box 76, Box 128, Folder 4)
  - October League (Marxist-Leninist) II, 1972-1976 (Box 76)
  - October League (Marxist-Leninist) III, 1972-1976 (Box 76)
  - Off Campus College Meeting at SUNY Binghamton (New York), 2001 (Box 76)
  - Off Center Theatre, 1984- (Box 76)
  - Office for Political Prisoners and Human Rights in Chile, 1976- (Box 76)
  - Office of the Permanent Observer of the Republic of Vietnam to the United Nations, undated (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Office Workers United, 1975 (Box 76)
  - Ohio Civil Rights Commission, undated (Box 76)
  - Ohio Farm Bureau Development Corporation, 1937, undated (Box 76)
  - Ohio Peace Action Council, undated (Box 76)
  - Ohio School of Social Science, 1933-1945 (Box 76)
  - Ohio State University: Center for Labor Research, 1996- (Box 76)
  - Old Timers, 1946 (Box 76)
  - Older Women's Liberation, undated (Box 76)
  - Oltrecortina I, 1954-1957 (Box 76)
  - Oltrecortina II, 1954-1957 (Box 76)
  - One Big Union Club, 1936, undated (Box 76)
  - One Incorporated (Los Angeles, CA), 1961 (Box 76)
  - One Term President, 2002 (Box 76)
  - Oneida Community (New York), circa 1901 (Box 76)
  - Ontological Hysteric Theater, 2004 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Open Media, 2002- (Box 76)
  - Operation Education/ Operation Bootstrap: Pamphlets (Los Angeles, CA), 1968 (Box 76)
  - Operation Freedom (Cincinnati, OH), 1961-1968 (Box 76)
  - Operation Move-in Coalition (Westside 35), 1970 (Box 76)
  - Operation Socialism, undated (Box 76)
  - Opposition Leniniste (France), 1927 (Box 76)
  - Organisation Armee Secrete, 1962 (Box 76)
  - Organization, the, undated (Box 76)
  - Organization Committee for a Revolutionary Workers Party (New York, NY), undated (Box 76)
  - Organization Communiste Internationaliste, 1973 (Box 76)
  - Organization for a Free Society (New York), 2010- (Box 76)
  - Organization Montoneros (Argentina), 1977 (Box 76)
  - Organization of Arab Unity: NYU Branch, undated (Box 76)
  - Organization of Asian Women, undated (Box 76)
  - Organization of Communist Workers (M-L) (Canada), 1977 (Box 76)
  - Organization of the Solidarity of the Peoples of Africa, Asia and Latin America (OSPAAL), 1966-1970 (Box 76)
  - Organized Community of United People (C.O.U.P.), 2002, undated (Box 76)
  - Organized Labor Capital Corporation (New York, NY), undated (Box 76)
  - Organizing Committee for a Fifth Estate (Washington, DC), 1974 (Box 76)
  - Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization, 1977 (Box 76)
  - Organizing Committee for a New African Support Committee, undated (Box 76)
  - Organizzazione Comunista Internazionalista, 2001 (Box 76)
  - Ottawa--Hull Area Council, 1935-1948 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Our Cooperative Cafeteria (New York, NY), 1922 (Box 76)
  - Our Generation: Pamphlets and Publications I, 1964-1970, undated (Box 76)
  - Our Generation: Pamphlets and Publications II, 1964-1970, undated (Box 76)
  - Our Generation: Pamphlets and Publications III, 1964-1970, undated (Box 76)
  - Our Generation: Pamphlets and Publications IV, 1964-1970, undated (Box 76)
  - Our Generation: Pamphlets and Publications V, 1964-1970, undated (Box 76)
  - Our Generation: Pamphlets and Publications VI, 1964-1970, undated (Box 76)
  - Ouvriers Belges en Belgique (Belgium Workmen), 1916 (Box 76)
- P, 1895-2011; 8.5 Linear Feet in 8 record cartons and 1 manuscript box
  - Pacesetters, 1971-1977, undated (Box 77)
  - Pacific Coast Labor School (Berkeley, CA), 1941 (Box 77)
  - Pacific News Service, undated (Box 77)
    Materials in this file are related to Japanese farmers.
  - Pacific Northwest Labor History Association (Seattle, WA), 1995- (Box 77)
  - Pacific Northwest Research Center (Eugene, OR), 1974- (Box 77)
  - Pacific Publishing Foundation, undated (Box 77)
  - Pacific Rim Coalition, undated (Box 77)
  - Pacific Street Films (Brooklyn, NY), 1981 (Box 77)
  - Pacific Studies Center, 1970 (Box 77)
  - Pacifica Radio, circa 1970, undated (Box 77)
  - Pacifica Radio Archive, 1980- (Box 77)
  - Painters Free Press, 1966 (Box 77)
  - Palestine Activist Forum (New York), undated (Box 77)
  - Palestine Children's Relief Fund, 2003 (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Palestine Human Rights Campaign, 1981- (Box 77)
  - Palestine Solidarity Committee, 1976-, undated (Box 77)
  - Pamphlet Press, 1945 (Box 77)
  - Pan Africanist Congress of Anzania, 1977-1979 (Box 77)
  - Pan-Pacific Trade Union Conference (Hankow, China), 1927 (Box 77)
  - Panorama DDR, 1985 (Box 77)
  - Paper Tiger Television, 2007- (Box 77)
  - Paris American Committee for July 4 Demonstration, undated (Box 77)
  - Park Slope Greens (New York), 2002 (Box 77)
  - Partai Sosialis Indonesia: Pamphlet, 1956 (Box 77)
  - Parti Communiste de Belgique, 1936 (Box 77)
  - Parti Communiste Francais, 1937 (Box 77)
  - Parti Communiste Francais: Opposition Leniniste, 1927 (Box 77)
  - Parti Communiste Internationaliste, 1961 (Box 77)
  - Parti Democratique de Guinee, 1959 (Box 77)
  - Parti Socialiste Belge, 1909- (Box 77)
  - Parti Socialiste (France), undated (Box 77)
  - Parti Socialiste SFIO (France) I, 1938- (Box 77)
  - Parti Socialiste SFIO (France) II, 1938- (Box 77)
  - Parti Socialiste SFIO (France) III, 1938- (Box 77)
  - Parti Socialiste Unifie (France), 1968 (Box 77)
  - Parti Unifie des Communistes Haitiens, 1981 (Box 77)
  - Partido Comunista de Colombia: Comite Central, undated (Box 77)
  - Partido Comunista de Cuba, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Partido Comunista do Brazil, 1946-1964 (Box 77)
  - Partido Comunista de Venezuela, 1946 (Box 77)
  - Partido Comunista Português, 1965 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Partido Mexicano Socialista, circa 1921 (Box 77)
  - Partido Revolucionario Institucional, 1949 (Box 77)
  - Partido Socialista Argentino, 1925 (Box 77)
  - Partido Socialista Democratico (Argentina), 1962 (Box 77)
  - Partido Socialista Puertorriqueno, 1975- (Box 77)
  - Partido Vanguardia Revolucionaria (Peru), 1978 (Box 77)
  - Partij Van de Arbeid, 1948 (Box 77)
  - Partisan Defense Committee, 1976- (Box 77)
  - Partisan Party, 1971 (Box 77)
  - Partisan Defense Committee, 1976- (Box 77)
  - Partito Comunista Italiano, 1979 (Box 77)
  - Partito Comunista Unificato D'Italia, undated (Box 77)
  - Partizdat Tsk VKP, 1932- (Box 77)
  - Party for Socialism and Liberation, 2004, undated (Box 77)
  - Party for Workers Power, 1974 (Box 77)
  - Party of Labour of Albania, 1961-1966 (Box 77)
  - Pastors for Peace, 1993-, undated (Box 77)
  - Patriot Party, 1970 (Box 77)
  - Patriotic Research Bureau in Defense of Christianity and Americanism, 1941 (Box 77)
  - Paul Robeson International Settlement (Detroit, MI), 1983- (Box 77)
  - Pax Christi (NYU), undated (Box 77)
  - Peace Action, 2009- (Box 78)
  - Peace Action Center (Washington, DC), 1962- (Box 78)
  - Peace Action Committee (Nutley, NJ), 1972 (Box 78)
  - Peace Action Council of Southern California, 1971 (Box 78)
  - Peace Action Education Fund, undated (Box 78)
  - Peace Action New York State, undated (Box 78)
  - Peace Activities Coordinating Council (PACC) (Los Angeles, CA), undated (Box 78)
  - Peace and Freedom Association, 1969 (Box 78)
  - Peace Association of Friends in America, 1915 (Box 78)
  - Peace Corps, 1962 (Box 78)
  - Peace Council of the German Democratic Republic, 1969-1971 (Box 78)
  - Peace Development Fund, 1995- (Box 78)
  - Peace for Cuba International Appeal, 1981 (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - Peace House (New York, NY), 1925 (Box 78)
  - Peace Information Center, 1950- (Box 78)
  - Peace Literature Service, 1960 (Box 78)
  - Peace Museum (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 78)
  - Peace News Ltd: Pamphlets, 1946-1954 (Box 78)
  - Peace Patriots, circa 1932 (Box 78)
  - Peace Pledge Union: Activist Group, undated (Box 78)
  - Peace Publications Committee, 1964 (Box 78)
  - Peace Publications -- Government Sponsorship of the Arts: Pamphlet, 1961 (Box 78)
  - Peace Through Change That Begins With Me, undated (Box 78)
  - Peace Treaty Campaign, 1988 (Box 78)
  - Peacemakers (New York, NY), undated (Box 78)
  - PeacePAC, 1982 (Box 78)
  - Peacesmith, Inc., undated (Box 78)
  - Peking Review: Pamphlets, 1973 (Box 78)
  - Penicillin For Vietnam, undated (Box 78)
  - Pennsylvania Child Labor Association, 1907, 1928 (Box 78)
  - Pennsylvania Civil Liberties Committee, 1932 (Box 78)
  - Pennsylvania Committee for Total Disarmament, 1924-1935 (Box 78)
  - Pennsylvania Committee to Defend the Pittsburgh Six, undated (Box 78)
  - Pennsylvania Fair Employment Practice Commission, 1955 (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad Voluntary Relief Department, 1952 (Box 78)
  - Pennsylvania Woman Suffrage Association, 1915 (Box 78)
  - Penny Phone League (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 78)
  - Pentagon Papers Fund, 1970s (Box 78)
  - Pentagon Papers Peace Project, undated (Box 78)
  - People Against Racism, 9164, undated (Box 78)
  - People Before Profits, undated (Box 78)
  - People for Peace, 1971 (Box 78)
  - People for Peace (Columbia University, New York, NY), 2002 (Box 78)
  - People for the American Way, undated (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - Peoples Translation Service, 1973-1974 (Box 128, Folder 18)
  - People to Abolish Abortion Laws, circa 1969 (Box 78)
  - People United for Affirmative Action (PUFAA), undated (Box 78)
  - People United for Justice, 1979 (Box 78)
  - People v Ashcroft, undated (Box 78)
  - People's Alliance, 1980 (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - Peoples' Alliance, 1979-1980 (Box 78)
  - People's Anti-War Mobilization, 1981-1987 (Box 78)
  - People's Bicentennial Commission I, 1973- (Box 78)
  - People's Bicentennial Commission II, 1973- (Box 78)
  - People's Campaign-Justice @ Wal-Mart, 2002 (Box 78)
  - People's Coalition for Peace and Justice I, 1971-1973 (Box 78, Box 128, Folder 15)
  - People's Coalition for Peace and Justice II, 1971-1973, undated (Box 78)
  - People's Coffee Grounds (New York, NY), 1970- (Box 78)
  - People's Coffee House (New York, NY), undated (Box 78)
  - People's College (Fort Scott, KS), undated (Box 78)
  - People's Committee, 1942 (Box 78)
  - People's Committee Against Hearst (Washington, DC), undated (Box 78)
  - People's Committee Against Pogroms in Poland, circa 1936 (Box 78)
  - Peoples' Congress of Apllied Religion, undated (Box 78)
  - People's Convention (London, U.K.), 1941 (Box 78)
  - People's Cooperating Communities Trucking Collective, 1975 (Box 78)
  - People's Co-operative State Bank (Hammond, IN), 1923, undated (Box 78)
  - People's Council of America for Democracy and Peace, 1917, undated (Box 78)
  - People's Court Comrades, 1975-1976 (Box 78)
  - People's Culture Union of America, 1948 (Box 78)
  - People's Drama, 1934 (Box 78)
  - People's Educational Center (Hollywood, CA), 1944-1946 (Box 78)
  - People's Education Forum, undated (Box 128, Folder 16)
  - People's Fund, the, 1980 (Box 78)
  - People's History Museum (Great Britain), 2002- (Box 78)
  - Peoples' House, 1918 (Box 78)
  - People's Information Center/ New York Switchboard, undated (Box 78)
  - People's Information Relay, 1978 (Box 78)
  - People's Institute, circa 1914, undated (Box 78)
  - People's Institute of Applied Religion, 1944- (Box 78)
  - People's Law School (San Francisco, CA), 1974 (Box 78)
  - People's Lawsuit to Set Aside the 1972 Elections (Box 78)
  - People's League, undated (Box 78)
  - People's Legislative Service, 1924-1925 (Box 78)
  - People's Life Fund, 1971 (Box 78)
  - People's Lobby I, 1930-1949 (Box 78)
  - People's Lobby II, 1930-1949 (Box 78)
  - People's May Day Committee, undated (Box 78)
  - People's Museum (Woodside, NY), circa 1970s (Box 78)
  - People's Party (Milwaukee, WI), 1973 (Box 78)
  - People's Party (New York, NY), 1936-1937 (Box 78)
  - People's Party (Washington, DC), 1971-1974 (Box 78)
  - People's Party of the United States of America, 1947 (Box 78)
  - People's Peace Treaty, 1971, undated (Box 79)
  - People's Platform Conference (New York, NY), 1970 (Box 79)
  - People's Power League, 1920 (Box 79)
  - People's Press (Minneapolis, MN), 1916 (Box 79)
  - People's Press I, 1969- (Box 79)
  - People's Press II, 1969- (Box 79)
  - People's Print, undated (Box 79)
  - People's Progress Slate, 1965 (Box 79)
  - People's Progressive Party (Guyana), 1971, undated (Box 79, Box 128, Folder 17)
  - People's Publishing House Ltd Bombay, 1953 (Box 79)
  - People's Reconstruction League, undated (Box 79)
  - People's Russian Information Bureau (London, U.K.), 1919 (Box 79)
  - People's School for Marxist Studies (New York, NY), 1983- (Box 79)
  - People's Songs, Inc. (Pete Seeger), undated (Box 79)
  - Pere Lachaise Cemetery (Paris, France), undated (Box 79)
  - Permanent International Committee for Recognition of the GDR, 1971 (Box 79)
  - Permanent Revolution Group, 1987-1988 (Box 79)
  - Peter Miller Films, Inc., 2001 (Box 79)
  - Peter V. Cacchione Association, undated (Box 79)
  - Petrograd Council of Workers' and Soldiers' Deputies, 1917 (Box 79)
  - Peuple, 1932 (Box 79)
  - Phelps-Dodge Workers' Defense Committee, undated (Box 79)
  - Phelps-Stokes Fund: Emergency Committee for African Refugees, 1982 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Free Press, 1971 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Gay Liberation Front, 1970 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Marxist School, 1990 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Reproductive Rights Coalition, undated (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia School of Social Science and Art, undated (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Solidarity, 1973- (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Tageblatt, 1936 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Women's Trade Union League, 1921 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Workers' Organizing Committee, 1977, undated (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Workers School, 1939 (Box 79)
  - Philadelphia Yearly Meeting of the Religious Society of Friends: Civil Liberties Committee, 1954 (Box 79)
  - Philippine Resource Center (Berkeley, CA), 1980s (Box 79)
  - Philippine-Vietnam Society, 1966 (Box 128, Folder 19)
  - Philippine Workers Support Committee, undated (Box 79)
  - Phoenix Anarchist Coalition (Ann Arbor, MI), 1969 (Box 79)
  - Physicians for a National Health Program, 2010- (Box 79)
  - Physicians for Social Responsibility, 1967 (Box 79)
  - Picture the Homeless (New York, NY), 2010, undated (Box 79)
  - Piedmont Rural Research Cooperative, 1966 (Box 79)
  - Pierre Degeyter Club (New York, NY), 1935 (Box 79)
  - Pig International Party, 1968 (Box 79)
  - Piney Woods School, 1950- (Box 79)
  - Pink Sheet on the Left (Washington, DC), 1980 (Box 79)
  - Pioneer Aid and Support Association, 1927 (Box 79)
  - Pioneer Book Service (London, U.K.), 1968 (Box 79)
  - Pioneer Women I, 1929- (Box 79)
  - Pioneer Women II, 1929- (Box 79)
  - Pioneer Youth of America, 1925-1948 (Box 79)
  - Pioneers for Women's Rights, undated (Box 79)
  - Pittsburgh Civil Rights Congress, 1952-1955 (Box 79)
  - Pittsburgh Marxist Study Group, undated (Box 79)
  - Pittsburgh Socialist Education League, undated (Box 79)
  - Plain Talk -- Catholic Information Society: Pamphlets, 1947, undated (Box 79)
  - Planetary Citizens, 1972 (Box 79)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1970 (Box 79, Box 128, Folder 21)
  - Planned Parenthood - World Population, 1970-1974 (Box 79)
  - Planning Council of America, undated (Box 79)
  - Play School Conference, undated (Box 79)
  - Plebs League (Great Britain), 1909-1949 (Box 79)
  - Ploughshares: Returned Peace Corps Volunteers Working for Peace (Seattle, WA), 1984 (Box 79)
  - Plumb Plan League (Washington, DC), undated (Box 79)
  - Pluto Press I, 1971- (Box 79)
  - Pluto Press II, 1971- (Box 79)
  - Pluto Press III, 1971- (Box 79)
  - PM Press, 2008- (Box 79)
  - Poale-Zion/ Zeire Zion, 1933, undated (Box 79)
  - Point Blank (Berkeley, CA), 1972-1973 (Box 79)
  - Point of Production: Marxist Journal, 1976 (Box 79)
  - Polemic Publishers, 1934-1935 (Box 80)
  - Policy Alternatives for the Caribbean and Central America (PACCA), 1987, undated (Box 80)
  - Polish-American Labor Council (Chicago, IL), 1945 (Box 80)
  - Polish-American Trade Union Committee, 1941 (Box 80)
  - Polish Committee of the Defenders of Peace (Warsaw, Poland), undated (Box 80)
  - Polish Information Center, 1944, undated (Box 80)
  - Polish Labor Group (New York, NY), 1943-1944 (Box 80)
  - Polish Labor Underground Press, undated (Box 80)
  - Polish Socialist Alliance, 1946 (Box 80)
  - Polish Socialist Party (Polska Partia Socjalistyczna): Delegation for Abroad, 1945-1947 (Box 80)
  - Polish United Workers Party (Poslka Zjednoczona Partia Robotnicza), 1950 (Box 80)
  - Political Action for Peace (Cambridge, MA), undated (Box 80)
  - Political Education and Action Collective (New York, NY), undated (Box 80)
  - Political Education Project (Boston, MA), 1973-1974 (Box 80)
  - Political Prisoners Defense and Relief Committee (New York, NY), 1919 (Box 80)
  - Political Prisoners Relief Committee (New York, NY), 1954 (Box 80)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund (New York, NY) I, 1976-1987, undated (Box 80, Box 128, Folder 22)
  - Political Rights Defense Fund (New York, NY) II, 1976-1987, undated (Box 80)
  - Political Science Pocket Library (New York, NY) (pamphlet), 1931 (Box 80)
  - Political Victims' Welfare Committee, undated (Box 80)
  - Politics Club (University of Chicago, IL), 1950- (Box 80)
  - Poor People's Campaign, 1968 (Box 80, Box 128, Folder 23)
  - Poor People's Corporation (Jackson, MS), circa 1970s (Box 80)
  - Porcupine Freedom Festival, 2011 (Box 80)
  - Porcupine Press: Catalog, 1995 (Box 80)
  - Positive Force DC, undated (Box 128, Folder 24)
  - Post War World Council (New York, NY), 1942-1964 (Box 80)
  - Post War World Council (New York, NY): Pamphlets I, 1942-1963 (Box 80)
  - Post War World Council (New York, NY): Pamphlets II, 1942-1963 (Box 80)
  - Potemkin Bookshop: Booklet, undated (Box 80)
  - Potomac Cooperative Federation (Washington, DC), 1948 (Box 80)
  - Pour Une Intervention Communiste (Paris), undated (Box 80)
  - Pouren Defense Conference (New York, NY), 1909 (Box 80)
  - Poverty/ Rights Action Center (Washington, DC), 1966 (Box 80)
  - Prairie Fire Organizing Committee, 1970s (Box 80)
  - Prairie School for Social Advance (Winnipeg, Canada), 1930-1945 (Box 80)
  - Praja Socialist Party (New Delhi, India), 1955, undated (Box 80)
  - Press Association of Jamaica, undated (Box 80)
  - Prime Time, 1972 (Box 80)
  - Princeton Area Sanctuary Committee, 1986-1987 (Box 80)
  - Princeton University: Industrial Relations Section (New Jersey) I, 1929-1957 (Box 80)
  - Princeton University: Industrial Relations Section (New Jersey) II, 1929-1957 (Box 80)
  - Prison Activist Resource Center (Berkeley, CA), 1999- (Box 80)
  - Prison Comfort Club (Chicago, IL), 1918 (Box 80)
  - Prison Moratorium Project, circa 1996- (Box 80)
  - Prisoners' Information and Support Service (Boston, MA), 1969 (Box 80)
  - Prisoners' Relief Committee, undated (Box 80)
  - Prisoners' Rights Union, 1994 (Box 80)
  - Prisoners' Strike for Peace, undated (Box 80)
  - Prisoners Solidarity Committee (New York, NY), 1972- (Box 80)
  - Prisoners Solidarity Committee: Pamphlets (New York, NY), 1972- (Box 80)
  - Prisoners Union (California), 1971-1975 (Box 80)
  - Private Health Insurance Must Go! Campaign, undated (Box 80)
  - Privatization of Culture Project (NYU), 2000 (Box 80)
  - Probe Magazine's Communications Workshop, undated (Box 80)
  - Pro-Democracy Campaign, undated (Box 80)
  - Program of the National Liberation Front of South Vietnam, undated (Box 80)
  - Progress Books (Toronto, Canada), 1964-1986 (Box 80)
  - Progress Publishers: Pamphlets, 1920, 1966-1975 (Box 80)
  - Progress Theatre, 2002 (Box 80)